History From The Hill UP085
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
History From The Hill
1999 -- 2013
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
International Letters and Visual Studies
UP085
20 Digital Object(s)
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains issues of "History from the Hill." It is the official newsletter for the Department of History. The original department newsletter had a different name and is not available on its website. However, in 1999 the department collected feedback from department members in order to rename the newsletter, and the name "History from the Hill" was ultimately chosen after it was suggested anonymously. The first issue was released in May 1999.
- History From The Hill, 1999 -- 2013; UP085.001; 20 Digital Object(s)
  Scope and Contents
  >"History from the Hill" is the official newsletter for the Department of History. The original department newsletter had a different name and is not available on its website. However, in 1999 the department collected feedback from department members in order to rename the newsletter, and the name "History from the Hill" was ultimately chosen after it was suggested anonymously. The first issue was released in May 1999.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - History from the Hill, 1999; UP085.001.001.00001; Department of History
    Volume, issue
    5, 5
  - History from the Hill, 1999; UP085.001.001.00002; Department of History
    6, 1
  - History from the Hill, 2000; UP085.001.001.00003; Department of History
    6, 2
  - History from the Hill, 2000; UP085.001.001.00004; Department of History
    6, 3
  - History from the Hill, 2000; UP085.001.001.00005; Department of History
    7, 1
  - History from the Hill, 2000; UP085.001.001.00006; Department of History
    7, 2
  - History from the Hill, 2001; UP085.001.001.00007; Department of History
    7, 3
  - History from the Hill, Fall, 2001; UP085.001.001.00008; Department of History
    8, 1
  - History from the Hill, Fall, 2002; UP085.001.001.00009; Department of History
    9, 1
  - History from the Hill, Spring, 2003; UP085.001.001.00010; Department of History
    9, 2
  - History from the Hill, Fall, 2003; UP085.001.001.00011; Department of History
    10, 1
  - History from the Hill, Fall, 2004; UP085.001.001.00012; Department of History
    11, 1
  - History from the Hill, Fall, 2005; UP085.001.001.00013; Department of History
    12, 1
  - History from the Hill, Fall, 2006; UP085.001.001.00014; Department of History
    13, 1
  - History from the Hill, Fall, 2007; UP085.001.001.00015; Department of History
    14, 1
  - History from the Hill, Fall, 2008; UP085.001.001.00016; Department of History
    15, 1
  - History from the Hill, Fall, 2009; UP085.001.001.00017; Department of History
    16, 1
  - History from the Hill, 2011; UP085.001.001.00018
    Fall
    XVIII, I
  - History from the Hill, 2012 -- 2013; UP085.001.001.00019
    Winter-Spring
    XIX, I
  - History from the Hill, 2013; UP085.001.001.00020
    XX, I